[
  {
    "id": "1",
    "question": "Anzac Day is held on?",
    "öptions": [
      {
        "type": "a",
        "option": "24 April"
      },
      {
        "type": "b",
        "option": "25 April"
      },
      {
        "type": "c",
        "option": "26 April"
      },
      {
        "type": "d",
        "option": "27 April"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "question": "The first Anzac Day commemoration occurred in?",
    "öptions": [
      {
        "type": "a",
        "option": "1915"
      },
      {
        "type": "b",
        "option": "1916"
      },
      {
        "type": "c",
        "option": "1939"
      },
      {
        "type": "d",
        "option": "1990"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "question": "ANZAC stands for?",
    "öptions": [
      {
        "type": "a",
        "option": "Australian and New Zealand Army Corps"
      },
      {
        "type": "b",
        "option": "Australian and New Zealand Artillery Company"
      },
      {
        "type": "c",
        "option": "American and New Zealand Army Corps"
      },
      {
        "type": "d",
        "option": "Australian and New Zealand Army Club"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "question": "A symbol commonly associated with Anzac Day is?",
    "öptions": [
      {
        "type": "a",
        "option": "A Kiwi"
      },
      {
        "type": "b",
        "option": "A Silver Fern"
      },
      {
        "type": "c",
        "option": "A red Poppy"
      },
      {
        "type": "d",
        "option": "A Yellow Rose"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "question": "Apart from the poppy what plant holds special significance on Anzac Day?",
    "öptions": [
      {
        "type": "a",
        "option": "Oregano"
      },
      {
        "type": "b",
        "option": "Rosemary"
      },
      {
        "type": "c",
        "option": "Basil"
      },
      {
        "type": "d",
        "option": "Thyme"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "question": "What is the Gallipoli Campaign also known as?",
    "options": [
      {
        "type": "a",
        "option": "Battle of Passchendaele"
      },
      {
        "type": "b",
        "option": "Somme Offensive"
      },
      {
        "type": "c",
        "option": "Champagne-Marne"
      },
      {
        "type": "d",
        "option": "Dardanelles Campaign"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "question": "How long did the battle at Gallipoli last?",
    "options": [
      {
        "type": "a",
        "option": "2 months"
      },
      {
        "type": "b",
        "option": "6 months"
      },
      {
        "type": "c",
        "option": "10 months"
      },
      {
        "type": "d",
        "option": "18 months"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "question": "Te Papa’s famous Gallipoli exhibition is called what?",
    "options": [
      {
        "type": "a",
        "option": "Gallipoli: The Scale of our War"
      },
      {
        "type": "b",
        "option": "The ANZACs and Gallipoli"
      },
      {
        "type": "c",
        "option": "New Zealand in World War I"
      },
      {
        "type": "d",
        "option": "War and the Aftermath"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "question": "What is the Last Post?",
    "options": [
      {
        "type": "a",
        "option": "A poem"
      },
      {
        "type": "b",
        "option": "A bugle call"
      },
      {
        "type": "c",
        "option": "A book"
      },
      {
        "type": "d",
        "option": "A campaign"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "question": "Who wrote the poem For the Fallen (Famous for its fourth stanza that begins with “They shall grow not old, as we that are left grow old”?",
    "options": [
      {
        "type": "a",
        "option": "Edgar Allan Poe"
      },
      {
        "type": "b",
        "option": "John Greenleaf Whittier"
      },
      {
        "type": "c",
        "option": "Laurence Binyon"
      },
      {
        "type": "d",
        "option": "Emily Dickinson"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "c"
  }
]
